(Leonard:)- Two hundred.
- Man, you're killing me.
(Stuart:)Two ten and I'm losing money.
Oh, no, we can't let him lose money,
Leonard. I'm so sorry.
(Leonard:)Two ten and you throw in
the Iron Man helmet.
(Stuart:)Are you crazy? That helmet's
signed by Robert Downey, Jr.
(Leonard:)So?
If you're gonna question
the importance of a signature...
(Stuart:)...on a plastic helmet from a movie
based on a comic book...
(Stuart:)...then all of our lives
have no meaning.
- Okay, fine. Just the sword, 210.
- Thank you. I can eat meat this week.
I've long said that what you lack
in academic knowledge...
(Sheldon:)...you make up for in street smarts.
- You want me to wrap it?
- No, it's okay.
(Leonard:)I'm gonna stab my friend in the chest.
- Hey, Stuart.
- Ah, hey, Wil.
(Sheldon:)Hello, Wil Wheaton.
- Hi, Sheldon. Nice sword.
- It's part of my sword collection.